Alan!
I have to meet Larry for dinner.
Are you ready yet?
ALAN:
The question is: are you?
(muffled):
Happy anniversary, baby.
What?
Six months ago today,
we cheated on Larry
for the first time.
So, to commemorate the occasion,
you donned the traditional
balloon underpants?
Exactly.
I have a "heart-on"
for you.
Charming.
Yeah, I was gonna get you
a dozen roses,
but I-I thought
the balloons were cuter.
Cheaper.
Six of one, half off the other.
I'm not sure this is something
we should be celebrating.
Come on, you have loved
every chapter
in our book of forbidden trysts.
That magical night in the
handicapped stall at Chili's.
The time we put a scare into
that field trip of sixth graders
at the planetarium
when they saw Uranus.
That weekend that
Larry went back east
and we went "down south."
Alan... I don't have
time for this.
Well, then open your present.
Spoiler alert: it's my penis
and two of his friends.
And you can't return it
if it's the wrong size.
As fun as all this is,
I only have about ten minutes
before I have to go meet Larry,
so we got to make this quick.
Ooh, my specialty.
First, I'm getting
rid of these balloons.
Oh. Oh.
I-I should've had you
blow them up.
(high-pitched):
I know what you like, baby.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x14 ♪
Three Fingers of Creme de Menthe
Original Air Date on February 6, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hey, bitches.
Hey.
What are you guys up to tonight?
Oh, dinner and game night.
My ex-wife and I
used to do that.
Our favorite game was Life,
until she ruined mine.
Yeah, we're more fans of
Monopoly, Backgammon...
Hungry Hungry Lesbos.
It's like Hungry Hungry Hippos,
but we don't eat balls.
How do you know
when you've won that game?
Trust me, you know.
Hey, something smells good.
Yeah, we play that, too.
Hey, you guys want to
join us for dinner?
Oh, no, I can't.
I'm going to the movies.
Oh, Alan, you
want to join?
Is it a porn movie?
Why would I invite a guy
to watch a porn in a theater?
So nobody weird
sits next to you.
Well, going with you
wouldn't solve that problem.
Fine. Go watch
your porn by yourself.
I'm not watching a porn!
Uh-huh. And I don't
use your bathroom to poop.
Look, I can't go anyway,
'cause I'm having a drink
with my girlfriend's boyfriend.
Why don't you poop
in his toilet?
You're already
banging his girlfriend.
You got a flat tire.
I got a what?
I noticed it when I was
getting out of your car.
Why were you in my car?
Taking a nap.
Why were you
taking a nap in my car?
I was getting high,
and I just went to sleep.
Why were you
getting high in my car?!
Because you hide
your pot in the car!
Geez! Which one of us
is high, you or me?
(groans)
Great.
Either of you guys
got Triple-A?
You don't need Triple-A
when you got double D's.
Why don't you just
change it yourself?
Eh, sounds like
a lot of work.
I'll just buy a new car.
Or you could use
the spare tire and jack.
Oh, there's nothing in there.
Whoa... there's a trunk
under the trunk!
Somebody's never smuggled
anything out of Mexico.
Here, uh, you grab the spare,
I'll loosen the lug nuts.
Wow, you really know
what you're doing.
Yeah.
Well, I had a boyfriend
who was a mechanic.
WALDEN and JENNY:
A boyfriend?
Yeah. Well, I went through
a phase where I dated guys.
Huh, I thought
you were a gold star.
What's a "gold star"?
It's a lesbian term for someone
who's never been with a guy.
Hey, I'm a gold star.
Wait a second,
what about that story
about you skinny-dipping
at Boy Scout camp?
Well, I was drowning.
I had to grab ahold
of something.
Just happened to be Roger.
So, if you had met Walden
instead of me...
Oh, God, no.
(chuckles)
Wow, great.
I'm getting hypothetical
rejections now.
I'm sorry,
you're just not my type.
I was more into,
you know, "guy" guys.
I'm a "guy" guy.
Oh, please.
You made me come in your room
to kill a spider.
I'm allergic!
(chuckles):
Look, it's not a big deal.
Some guys fix things
and some guys
call the guys that fix things.
You know, right after
they watch Project Runway.
Oh, I didn't see it last night.
Don't tell me, don't tell me.
I rest my case.
You know what, I'll show you.
Here, give me that.
Okay.
Tell me I'm not a guy's guy.
I got "guy"
coming out of my ass.
Don't... (scoffs)
You know what I meant.
(groans)
God, these nuts
are hard to get off.
Oh, okay, I'll give you
that one. (laughs)
Hey, Jeff.
Hey, there he is.
The B-F-F of J-E-F-F.
(both laugh)
That's pretty good.
Did you just
come up with that?
What do you think,
I just sat here
jotting down rhymes
before you showed up?
I'll have a whiskey.
Oh, oh, we're doing
the hard stuff. Okay.
I'll have three fingers
of crème de menthe.
Yeah, I've just been
kind of in a funk lately.
What's going on?
It's Lyndsey.
Mm, Lyndsey. Lyndsey.
I'm sorry, uh,
Lyndsey is...?
My girlfriend.
Oh, yes, yes. You know,
I-I can never remember her name,
because, you know,
I never really knew her.
Doesn't matter.
Anyway, she dumped me.
She dumped you?!
(laughs):
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
I was so shocked,
my first reaction was wrong.
Yeah, well, it's been
a really rough two weeks.
Wait, two weeks?
You-you guys have been
broken up for two weeks
and this is the first
I'm hearing about it?
Oh, I'm sorry, buddy.
I should have told you sooner.
Well, someone
certainly should have.
Anyway, there is
one bright side:
at least now, you and I
are free to hang
whenever we want.
We couldn't before?
Well, I-I didn't really
want to tell you this, but...
Lyndsey didn't
like you very much.
She said that?
Yeah, she'd go on and on about
your hair and your clothes.
She even said you had
the worst taste in jewelry.
I don't know where she got that.
I mean, it's not like
you ever bought her jewelry.
That's true.
Although, if I had,
she wouldn't have noticed
unless I put it in
the bottom of her wine glass.
Women.
I know how to
kill this pain.
Bring me the bottle.
Yeah, better make it two.
Ooh, and a little
whipped cream.
(chuckles)
Oh, hey, Berta,
can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
I'm a man's man, right?
I thought that
when I first met you,
but then I found out
you were married to a woman.
No... no, I mean, like...
like, I'm a guy who can...
build things and...
a guy who can get horses
out of mud and...
...who, if-if he gets stabbed,
he just rubs dirt in it.
You're talking about
a guy's guy?
One of those dudes, like,
in the boner pill commercials?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
You're not one of those.
What?
Well, you're more like
one of those guys
that gets a mani-pedi.
Yeah, well, first of all,
there is nothing wrong
with taking care of yourself.
And second of all,
manicure has the word "man,"
like, right there in it.
Well, now, you calm down
manly man,
or you're gonna spill
your chamomile tea.
At least I'm the manliest man
in this house, right?
Um...
What?
Really? I'm under Alan?
Well, do you want
to be on top of him?
What did Jenny tell you?
I was drowning!
'Sup, ladies?
Hey, look who it is:
Bob the Builder.
Oh, yeah,
it's pretty manly, huh?
The only thing
manlier would be
if you were dressed
as the cop or the cowboy.
♪ Why... are you gay?
Is this about
the flat tire?
'Cause you have
nothing to prove.
Oh, I ain't provin' nothin'.
Just being a guy.
Doin' what guys do,
fixin' things.
And do not expect me
to get in touch with my emotions
or ask for directions
anytime soon.
(spits)
Is that chewing tobacco?
Yes, it is.
And it tastes terrible.
And I'm feeling dizzy.
Wow, very impressive.
(laughs)
You ain't seen nothing yet.
That there's a laser.
Badass.
Gee, oh, this here table
is two degrees from being level.
I got this!
There we go,
job well done.
I'm gonna need my band saw.
You two clean this up.
Ladies' work.
♪ Men. ♪
All right, I'm lubricated.
Let's do this thing.
So, uh, how was your dinner
with Larry the other night?
Fine.
Where did you go?
La Dolce.
What did you guys have?
Salmon.
Did Larry like it?
Okay, talking about
my boyfriend eating fish
is the world's worst foreplay.
Is he still eating
fish, Lyndsey?
Is he?
All right,
what's going on?
I'll tell you
what's going on.
Larry told me
you broke up with him.
Mm-hmm.
For the love of God,
you're still seeing Larry?!
As Jeff Strongman?
At least one of us
is faithful to him.
(Scoffs)
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't tell you because
I knew you'd just ask
when you and I are
getting back together.
That's not true.
When are we getting
back together?
Alan.
Oh, this is what
I've been waiting for
for the last six months.
We-we can finally be
together, honestly, openly.
I-I can prove to you
I'm the man that
you're supposed to be with.
I love you, Lyndsey.
Great. So you want
to get married?
Whoa, whoa, marriage?
We just got back together.
You're just like Larry.
Neither one of you
are willing to commit.
I'm just saying that maybe, you
know, we should date a while.
I mean, let's be honest,
you are a bit of an adulterer.
This is why I've been
avoiding this conversation.
You don't want to get married,
and I don't want to be with you
unless we do, so...
if that's the case, I don't know
what else to say, Alan.
(sighs):
Except...
good-bye.
Wow. (laughs)
Okay.
Okay. I mean...
Just so you know,
when I walk out this door,
I am never coming back.
This is the last you will see...
of Alan Harper.
(door closes)
(knocking)
Breakup sex?
Oh!
♪ Men. ♪
Hello.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Am I in your way?
The only thing in my way
are those pants.
(chuckles):
Oh, gee, sorry about that.
About the only crack around here
I ain't put caulk in.
(laughs)
All right.
Whoa! Look at that.
Good as new.
Hey, if there's anything around
here that needs fixin',
I'll be the one fixin' it.
So if you see something that's
broke and bothering you,
you just let me know.
(sighs):
Hey.
I see something that's
broke and bothering me.
I'm not in the mood, Berta.
I just got dumped.
Oh. What happened?
Well, you know,
I confronted Lyndsey
about breaking up with Larry,
and it blew up in my face.
Alan, Alan, Alan.
You know, relationships
are a lot like woodworking.
There's a certain way
that things fit together,
and if you force it,
it splinters and falls apart.
But if you take your time,
follow instructions,
you build something
beautiful and solid,
something you can be proud of.
Like this here elegant
cedar birdhouse.
What does this have to do
with me and Lyndsey?
Nothing.
But how cool is it
I built this?
It's even got a guest room
for the Alan birds.
If you listen real close,
you can hear them.
Cheap, cheap.
♪
(song ends)
Isn't this great?
What's cooler than going
to a strip club in the daytime?
The girls aren't always hot,
but the mozzarella sticks are.
(groans):
Uh... yeah.
You sound like me
two weeks ago.
I made that noise every time
I heard the name "Lyndsey."
(groans)
Yeah, that's it.
What's going on?
To be honest, I, uh...
had a bit of a
breakup myself.
Oh, geez.
Mm.
And here I am whining
about my problems.
Eh.
I'm sorry, Jeff.
If I have a flaw,
it's that sometimes
I'm not aware of things
that are going on around me.
It's actually one of the
things I like most about you.
So, what happened
between you and your girl?
Well, she wanted
to get married,
and I'm just not
sure I'm ready.
No way! That's the same
reason I lost Lyndsey.
It's like we were
dating the same woman.
It's exactly like that.
So, do you miss her?
Are you kidding?
I mean, she's the
only one for me.
I mean, she's the one who
brings me up when I'm down...
Whoa. Hello, future
Mrs. Strongman.
So, what are you
afraid of?
I don't know.
It's just such a big commitment.
Bottom line:
do you still love her?
Yes, I do.
Then you got to
get her back.
Don't make
the same mistake I did.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
I know I'm right.
Chances like this
only come along
once in a lifetime.
I'm gonna do it, Larry.
I am gonna ask her to marry me.
That-a-boy! And when
things work out,
I'm gonna be the best man
at you and your girl's wedding.
Well... we'll cross that
bridge when we come to it.
Want a private
dance?
Oh, sorry, I can't.
I have a date with destiny.
Destiny's off today.
Oh, no, I-I meant, uh, uh...
Never mind.
Why don't you take my friend.
It's on me.
Oh, I only have a 20.
Uh, you know what?
I think seven's fair.
(machine buzzing)
Walden?
Oh, hey!
Sorry, ladies!
(machine stops)
Man at work!
Wh-What are you doing?
Well, it's a little technical
for the layperson.
What the hell, let me
walk you through it.
What I'm doing is
sanding and re-staining,
when I recognized some
dry rot and termite damage.
And I thought to myself,
what the hell,
I got a couple hours--
why don't I just rebuild
this bad boy from scratch.
(giggles)
The bubbles tickle my nose.
Okay, you know what? You got
to stop building things.
I was wrong--
you are so manly
that if I were straight, I'd
totally bang your brains out.
Well, of course you would,
sweetheart.
But I'd probably
sleep with you once
and then never call you again.
Hold still, please.
Yep, they're level.
(clears throat)
(machine starts)
Ow!
Aah! Aah!
Mmm.
I'm just gonna rub some dirt
in it and keep going.
Walden! Hey...
What are you doing?
Oh, this? Well,
it's pretty technical
for the layperson.
What the hell, let me just...
No, doesn't matter,
doesn't matter.
Uh, I-I got big news.
I am gonna ask Lyndsey
to marry me.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I just have to get a ring.
I got a ring you could have.
The one I proposed to Zoey with.
I don't know,
that ring didn't work.
Neither do you.
(chuckles):
Touché.
Well, I can't believe my
best friend's getting married.
All right, come on,
bring it in.
Man hug.
Oh. Oh. You smell.
Oh, yeah.
It's awesome, isn't it?
I haven't showered in two days.
That's what guys do--
we stank.
You smell good...
bitch.
Ladies love flowers.
Um...
Oh, hey, Jeff!
Why are you calling me Jeff?
You must be here to see
your friend Larry,
who is also here.
Jeff? What are you
doing here?
(laughs):
Larry!
I-I just, uh, I
came by to-to...
yell at this one
over here
for breaking up with
my friend Larry.
Can you think of a better
reason for me to drop by?
'Cause I certainly can't.
Well, now that you're here, why
don't you have a drink with us.
Oh, I-I'm sure Jeff has
better places to be.
Work, nope.
Girlfriend, nope.
Taste in jewelry, nope.
Here you go.
Bottoms up, Lyndsey.
Not the first time
I've said that to her.
(groans)
What's this?
A ring?
What's going on?
Yeah, what
is going on?
Jeff helped me realize
I don't want to lose you.
These last two weeks
have been the worst
in my life.
I don't want to spend
another minute without you.
Okay, I think
she's heard enough.
Let's go get some
wings. Come on.
Ooh, wings.
Just let me
wrap this up real quick.
Lyndsey MacElroy,
you're my soul mate.
Will you marry me?
I can't believe
this is happening.
Yes, yes, I will marry you!
So, Jeff, how'd it go
with your girl?
Uh...
I was too late.
She's marrying someone else.
That was quick.
Wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
LARRY: You know what?
Forget her.
If she chose some jackass over
you, she's just a dumb whore.
Uh, she's-she's
actually really great.
No, she's not.
She and her new man
are both garbage.
(groans):
Uh...
♪ Men. ♪
Whoa, look at this.
That's right.
Hey, uh,
who has one and a half thumbs
and built this deck
all by himself?
This guy.
Well, I'm impressed.
I would've had
to call a guy.
Well, then my phone
would've rang,
because I am the guy.
Got to admit, I was
wrong about you.
That's all right.
We all make mistakes.
Oh! That's my spit cup.
This thing feels sturdy enough
for us to have sex on later.
WALDEN:
Oh, it is.
But, uh, be careful,
'cause I just
stained her.
Well, if you hadn't,
we would have.
Ah. Look at that.
Looks like somebody
needs a new roof.
Luckily, I know a guy.
(chuckles)
(wood crackling)
Whoa. Walden?
WALDEN:
Call a guy!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man